[Applause]
wow that was nice had me feeling like
Obama in his first term right there now
I felt very welcome look at this thank
you guys so much for being here how you
guys doing tonight you guys feeling good
great thank you for giving my name right
my name is J Whittaker some people have
a hard time with my last name it's a
super easy name it's a British last name
it's but sometimes people mispronounce
Whittaker I've gotten a wind talker
that's weird
I've gotten white taker hashtag
interracial dating uh gotten white
attackers sometimes I'm cranky on
Mondays you know how goes whatever no
I'm originally from Los Angeles
California
all right cool thank you thank you and
then I moved out to Orange County and
then I looked at my dad and said dad
it's not white enough I want to go to
Utah and this is the place yeah this is
the place yeah
it was the place right here
my dad's a great father he's a great
father like I love him he's like he's at
that point now where he's he's got a
smartphone but he's kind of dumb with it
you know like it's just you ever get a
selfie from a parent it's all blurry
there's like five different emojis that
don't belong there
and he's like he still lives in LA so
every time he's like sending me a selfie
or something like he's always just like
had like a Dodgers game or a Lakers game
just doing something really cool and he
always tried to brag he's like yeah look
at all this cool stuff now that I get
that now that you don't live with me
anymore yeah yeah oh man but I miss I
miss back home and you know like but my
dad moved me out of LA I lived there in
the eighties he thought I was gonna join
a gang you know but look at me I'm not
threatening in any way shape or form
I smile in all my photos you know I take
all the stickers off my hat you know I'm
one of the good ones but look at me like
I look like I got kicked out of NWA for
having good grades okay y'all heard it
easy I'm easy eh that's me I can help
you with calculus about the most
thuggish thing I ever did in my life was
one time I went to the movies
I brought some outside food or drink up
in there
right I'm trying to see Magic Mike
what's up I'm not gonna join a gang like
the Bloods or Crips come on now that's
just not it's not conducive if you ever
join a gang which you haven't they were
joined a gang you know they jump you in
for those who don't know what the jump
in that's where they just beat you up
and give you a handkerchief and tell you
that you're a part of something okay
that's not gonna work for me if I'm
gonna join a gang I'm gonna join a nice
white friendly gang like the Jets from
West Side Story because it's ten times
easier to join their gang it's way
easier don't believe me listen to song
when you're a jet you're a jet all the
way from your first cigarette to your
last dying day that's it I got a smoke
one cigarette and I'm in a gang and I
get to hold hands with a Puerto Rican
see let's do this total SDS yes that
means it means every day I read that
somewhere
subscribe to drive our comedy for even
more of the world's largest collection
of clean comedy